



PERSONAL

Mobile +92-333-1296558 panhwersadagat22@gmail.com **Email Birthday** 1st August 1997 Languages English, Urdu, Sindhi



ABOUT ME

I am an Android Developer, very passionate and dedicated to my work. I enjoy every step of the software development process form discussion and collaboration to concept and execution. More importantly, I am most satisfied when I deliver the final product as per users' requirement that is useful to them. Indeed, through my experience as an Android developer, I have acquired necessary skills and knowledge to make your project a success! I am always open to discuss the new project ideas.



PROFESSIONAL SKILL

- Android Development
- Java Development
- Kotlin
- Python
- Swift



SOCIAL LINK

- /Sadaqat-Panhwer
- in /Sadagat-Panhwer-47614615a/
- /Sadaqatsap



N Curriculum Vitae

SADAQAT ALI

ANDROID DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

BACHELORS DEGREE / 2017 - 2020

Currently in Finaly Year of Computer Science From University Of Sindh Jamshoro, Sindh

INTERMEDIATE / 2016

BISE Mirpurkhas

MATRICULATION / 2014

BISE Mirpurkhas

WORK EXPERIENCES

PREDIX ACADEMY

Worked as a Java Developer at Predix Academy June 2017 - August 2017

PREDIX ACADEMY

Worked as an Android Developer at Predix Academy June 2018 - July 2018

HNH TECH SOLUTION

Worked as an Android Developer at HNH Tech Solution June 2019 - August 2019

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Playing Games

Reading Books

Reading Newspapers

Social Media

PERSONAL SKILL

Creative

Management

Team Work

Innovate